{
    "subject": "Henry_IV_of_France",
    "predicate": "isMarriedTo",
    "object": "Marie_de'_Medici",
    "human_readable": "Henry IV of France is married to Marie de' Medici.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9089370369911194,
            "question": "To whom was Henry IV of France married?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9042761325836182,
            "question": "Who was the ruler of France who married Marie de' Medici?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8980258703231812,
            "question": "Was Marie de' Medici married to a French king?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8608040809631348,
            "question": "Who was married to Marie de' Medici?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8565077781677246,
            "question": "Who is the spouse of Henry IV of France?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7975778579711914,
            "question": "Was Henry IV of France ever married?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.735650360584259,
            "question": "What is the name of Henry IV of France's wife?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.720434308052063,
            "question": "Which historical figure is known for being married to Marie de' Medici?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3808978497982025,
            "question": "Who was the queen consort during the reign of Henry IV of France?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3767038583755493,
            "question": "What is the name of the queen consort of Henry IV of France?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Henry IV of France is married to Marie de' Medici.",
            "html": "yago_28032_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Who was the queen consort during the reign of Henry IV of France?",
            "html": "yago_28032_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Which historical figure is known for being married to Marie de' Medici?",
            "html": "yago_28032_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the name of Henry IV of France's wife?",
            "html": "yago_28032_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "yago_28032_116.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_28032_127.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_28032_17.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_28032_25.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_28032_44.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_28032_51.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_28032_66.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_28032_93.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_28032_98.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_28032_99.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the evaluation:\n\nThe triple \"Henry IV of France is married to Marie de' Medici\" can be formalized as:\n\n(?X = Henry IV of France) \u2227 (?Y = Marie de' Medici) \u2227 (married(?X, ?Y))\n\nEvaluating this triple based on the provided context information:\n\n* There are multiple mentions of \"Marie de M\u00e9dicis\" and \"Marie de' Medici\" being married to King Henry IV of France.\n* The documents consistently mention the marriage between Marie de' Medici/Marie de M\u00e9dicis and King Henry IV of France.\n\nTherefore, the evaluation result is:\n\n{'output': 'yes'}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents provide multiple instances confirming that King Henry IV of France was married to Marie de' Medici, including details about their marriage date and the context surrounding it."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": "is true",
            "full_ans": "0.9"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": "is true",
            "full_ans": "0.9"
        }
    },
    "final_decision": "true",
    "actual_decision": "true",
    "analysis": {
        "error_category": "caafscd",
        "error_detail": "cdscsd",
        "category": "csdcs",
        "stratum": "fwefew",
        "topic": "wefw"
    }
}